Ronak Thakkar

80/A, Jivaraj Park Society, Telephone Exchange road, Patan, Gujarat, IN. • +91 97249 84666 • thakkaronak.007@gmail.com • linkedin.com/in/ronak-thakkar5

Senior QA Test Engineer

Working as a Software QA Engineer with experience in Agile and Scrum methodologies. Skilled in manual testing, test case development and execution, cross-browser testing, website and mobile app testing, payment gateway testing, accessibility, and internationalization.

WORK EXPERIENCE

TechMahindra LIMITED · Ahmedabad QA Engineer

02/2022 - Present

• Performed end-to-end testing, including functional, regression, performance and API Testing tests using tools like JIRA, Trello Asana, GitHub, TestRail.

Working with Software testing with performing test cases, Hands-on Experience with Agile and Scrum.

- Currently working on E-Commerce Web App with well known MNC which include the flow from product Purchase to Order Return as well as i18n, with additional support of Ally Testing.
- Responsible for communicating with onsite clients starting from requirement understanding to successful feature releases.
- Handling USA & Singapore- based clients and engineers, Extended the services provided in India to Singapore extended that gave exponential revenue per application too.
- Performed Integration Testing, System testing, Compatibility Testing on all types of browsers.
- Performed end-to-end testing, including functional, regression, performance and API Testing tests using tools like JIRA, Trello Asana, Github, TestRail.

AddwebSolution PVT LTD · Ahmedabad Associate QA Engineer

01/2020 - 01/2022

ASSOCIALE QA ETIGITLEEI

- Working with Software testing with mobile, desktop and cross browser testing, with agile methodology GitLab, GitHub, Jira etc.
- Explored Automation Testing with Selenium and Appium and Performance Testing using JMeter, API Testing Postman.
- Key Projects handled individually and with a team: M13.co-Content Based Website, lladro.com An ECommerce WebApplication, aedu.co.in/- A School Management System WebApp.

$\textbf{Mind Inventory} \cdot \textbf{Ahmedabad}$

01/2020 - 01/2020

Android Developer

Android App Developer with from requirement understanding to happy launching

TechExtensor PVT LTD · Ahmedabad

01/2019 - 01/2019

Jr. Android Developer

• Explored the basics of android with java and used to call web services for the mobile apps.

EDUCATION

M.Sc. (CA& IT) in Computer Science

HNGUniversity • Patan, Gujarat, IN • GPA: 9.00

B.Sc. (CA& IT) in Computer Science

HNGUniversity • Patan, Gujarat, IN • GPA: 7.63

CERTIFICATIONS

ISTQB Foundation Level (CTFL)	10/2024 - Present
-------------------------------	-------------------

Udemy

ISTQB Advanced Level Agile Technical Tester (ATT) 10/2024 - Present

Udemy

The 50-minute Communication Guide 10/2024 - Present

Udemy

POSTMAN API Testing - Step by Step for Beginners 10/2024 - Present

Udemy

Learn Generative AI in Software Testing 10/2024 - Present

Udemy

NIELIT - CCC

National Institute of Electronics and Information Technology (NIELIT - CCC)

AWARDS & SCHOLARSHIPS

PAB Award (Pet On Back Award) 01/2023

TechMahindra Limited

PROJECTS

CabIndia- A Cab Service Project 01/2018

TechExtensor PVT LTD

Library Management System

DCS, HNGUniverisy

A Social Media Web Application

TechMahindra Limited

CabSahara- A Cab Project

TechExtensor PVT LTD

Clinical Trial System based app for clients

TechExtensor PVT LTD

StudyPlus provides powerful Dashboard statistics, including Total Patients, Total Studies, Total Segments, Total Message, Device ratio, Appointment Cancelations ratio, Recent Message/Notification detail.

VoxPop

Mind Inventory

VoxPop - It is a survey app created for the users of various age groups. The customer can send out the surveys which the users can fill.

Medicita

Mind Inventory

Medicita - A clinical Trial system - health care Project.

UFM

Mind Inventory

UFM - Whole App upgrade with latest Library, Plug-ins with latest trends.

Link4Prof

Mind Inventory

Link4Prof - It is a social media platform which helps users who are jobseekers to create a network among job providers and companies. It enables you to network with people and professional organizations in the industry.

M13.co

AddWeb Solution Pvt Limited

M13.co- A Content-based website.

lladro.com

AddWeb Solution Pvt Limited

lladro.com - An ECommerce WebApplication - Technology - magento.

AddWeb Education Management System

AEDU helps your management to be organized & precise all the time. Everything that you need to manage manually in your school can be done through this software. There are various panels & features supporting different functions necessary for your school management. A ERP Solution for School Management System - Web Application, Native App, Multi User Login Interface and many more.

SKILLS

- Manual Testing Methodologies
- Test Case
 Development and execution
- Cross browser testing
- Website and Mobile App Testing
- Accessibility (A11y)
- Internationalization (i18n)
- Payment gateway Testing
- Agile
- Scrum
- Appium

- Selenium
- JMeter
- Postman
- Helping Nature
- Team Management

Languages Known

- Gujarati
- Hindi
- English